

AL-HASSAN ABDUL-BAQI

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am a web developer/designer with over 3 years of experience in this field. I have skills in both frontend and backend languages such as;

html, css, javascript, node.js and react.js

. I have worked with various happy clients and this made them refer me to other people. I would definitely love to work with you on your next project.

CONTACT



+234-812-706-2635



alhassandamilola16@gmail.com



www.codemyhobby.com

EXPERTISE

Html5

CSS

Bootstrap

Javascript

React.js Node.js

WORK EXPERIENCE



Tamazingevents.com 2019-2022

Web Developer

I worked with tamazing event which is an event planning and decor company based in Dallas Texas. As the web developer of the company, I was in charge of the following duties;

- · Building and managing their website.
- Promoting the company's website on various social media platform.
- Bringing traffic to the company's website.



RAI HR Consulting 2022- 2023

Web Developer



Amazon Unite International 2023- Till Date

Web Developer



YOUTUBER @ CODEMYHOBBY

I am the CEO/FOUNDER of codemyhobby, which is a YouTube channel/business based on teaching programming languages and its benefit to the world.

EDUCATION



Lagos State University

2020 - till date

Bachelor in science

· Currently studying computer science